The Register to the Betsy Jolas Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, 1958-2006; Series I
  - Music by Jolas, 1
    - Works for unaccompanied chorus, 7
      - Motet 1 "To Everything There is a Season", 1946-04; 16 pages; Two published scores (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - La Nuit m'est Courte, 4 pages; Holograph in pencil. "Paris 19 Avril 1947." (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - A Nonsensical Birthday Rhyme, 2 pages; Holograph score in pencil. (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Perriault le Déluné, circa 70 pages; Holograph score in pencil with annotations. Includes notes, sketches, and fragments of text. (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Savez vous qui est mon ami?, 1956; 1 page (verso of "Le vent coule et s'en va"); Holograph score in pencil. (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Soeurs d'espérance, 2 pages; Holograph in ink. In folder with cover sheet: Choeurs politiques (1951-54). "Chérence 5 Sept 52." (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Sonate a 12 pour choeur mixte a 12 voix solistes, 44 pages; Holograph score in pencil with annotations and notes. Contains sketches. (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Sonate a 12 pour choeur mixte a 12 voix solistes, 58 pages; Photocopy of score with pencil annotations. (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Sonate a 12 pour choeur mixte a 12 voix solistes, 119 pages; Published score with pencil annotations and bound published score with pencil annotations, bound. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Works for solo voice or small vocal ensemble, 8
      - Caprice à Deux Voix, 4 pages; Lyrics sheets, typed and in pencil with annotations. (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Caprice a Deux Voix, 1978; 5 pages; Holograph score in ink. (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Caprice à 2 Voix, 1978; 6 pages; Lyric sheets and manuscript sketches in ink and pencil. (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Carillon d'été, 5 pages; Holograph score in pencil with annotations. (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Carillons d'hiver, 2006; 11 pages; Holograph score in pencil with several parts. (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Chanson de Mai, 1943; 3 pages; Holograph in pencil. For voice and oboe. (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Chansons pour Paule, 1951; 14 pages; Holograph in ink with annotations in pencil. Contents: Tulipe, La mer, Jeux de Construction, Lune, Orage, Le Puits, Au Télephone, Midi, Le petit marin, Mon Ours, Etoiles, Ma Chatte, Trottinette. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - D'un Journal d'Amour, 2009; 22 pages; Manuscript sketches in pencil (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - D'un Journal d'Amour, 2009; 7 pages; Holograph score in pencil (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Liring Ballade, 46 pages; Photocopy of manuscript with annotations in pencil. For baritone and orchestra. Dedicated to Eugene Jolas. "1e version; Partition création de J. Mercier; Chérence le 31 Aout 1980." (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Liring Ballade, 46 pages; Photocopy of manuscript with annotations in pencil. For baritone and orchestra. Dedicated to Eugene Jolas. "1e version; Partition création de J. Mercier; Chérence le 31 Aout 1980." (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Liring Ballade, 15 pages; Holograph sketches in pencil. "Liring Ballade fragments." (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Mon Ami, 1974; 1 page; Holograph score in pencil. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Mon Ami, 1974; 3 pages; Printed score with pencil annotations. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Motet IV, 59 pages; Holograph in pencil. "(in stile rappresentativo) sopra una lettera del Petrarca che narra l'ascensione a monte Ventoso (1353); Paris le 27 Avril 2002". (Box 11, Folder 5)
        Standard Title: Motet IV
      - Motet IV, 30 pages; Holograph in pencil. For soprano, flute, clarinet, harp, violin, and violoncello. (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Motet IV: L'Ascension du Mont Ventoux, 19 pages; Manuscript libretto in pencil with additional notes, original printed text, and relevant correspondence (Box 13, Folder 7)
        Standard Title: L'ascension du Mont Ventoux (Motet IV + interludes)
      - Motet IV: L'Ascension du Mont Ventoux, 16 pages; Text, notes, and composition plans. (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Motet IV: L'Ascension du Mont Ventoux, 2002; 65 pages; Published edition with annotations in pencil. Includes 2 photos of Betsy Jolas on Mt. Ventoux. For soprano, flute, clarinet, harp, violin, and violoncello. "(In stile rappresentativo) sopra una lettera del Petrarca che narra l'ascensione a monte Ventoso (1336)." (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - L'Ascension du Mont Ventoux: Interludes 1 a 20, 2003; 33 pages; Holograph score in pencil for interludes 1-20 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - L'Ascension du Mont Ventoux (Scenic Adaptation of Motet IV), 2007; 7 pages; Narrator booklet for staged performance in ink and pencil (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - L'Ascension du Mont Ventoux (Scenic Adaptation of Motet IV), 2007; 8 pages; Photocopy of narrator booklet for staged performance with annotations (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - L'Ascension du Mont Ventoux (Scenic Adaptation of Motet IV), 2003; 39 pages; Photocopy of score with annotations and sketches (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Mots: Sept piéces pour ensemble vocal de cinq voix solistes et huit instruments, 3 pages; Holograph sketches in pencil. Includes 2 pages of manuscript with sketches for Quatuor II, B for Sonata, and D'un opéra de Voyage. (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Mots: Sept piéces pour ensemble vocal de cinq voix solistes et huit instruments, 40 pages; Holograph in ink. "Paris, 31. 1. 63, 21. 21. 9. 63; Durée totale: 20' 40.'" (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Mots: Sept piéces pour ensemble vocal de cinq voix solistes et huit instruments, 38 pages; Photocopy of manuscript. Includes notes. "Paris le 31. 1. 63; Durée totale: 20' 40"; 1e version." (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Mots: Sept piéces pour ensemble vocal de cinq voix solistes et huit instruments, 45 pages; Photocopy of manuscript with annotations in pencil and ink. Missing pages 1-2. "Paris 31. 1. 63, 21. 21. 9. 63." (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - De Nuit: Deux chants à voix seule, 4 pages; Holograph in pencil. J'ignore – Dans l'obscurité. "Paris, 19 Septembre 2004, ca 2' 40; Paris le 23 Septembre 2004, ca 3' 25; A Noel Lee." (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - L'Oeil Égaré, 1961-2002; 22 pages; Computer generated score with pen and pencil annotations; "Six chants pour baryton et piano" (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - L'Oeil Égaré, 16 pages; Holograph score in ink and pencil with revisions. (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Petits carillons d'automne (canon à 3), 2006; 7 pages; Holograph score in pencil with annotations. (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Petits carillons d'Automne (canon à 3), 2006; 2 pages; Manuscript sketches in pencil. Intermingled with "Carillons d'Hiver." (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Petit Pierre: canon á 3 + ornaments, 2006; 1 pages; Holograph in ink. 3 voices and piano, harp, or guitar. (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Plupart du temps II, 1990; 5 pages; Holograph sketches in pencil. "1e version avec choeur abandonee." (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Plupart du temps II, 1989; 14 pages; Holograph in pencil. Includes 3 pages of notes. "Paris le 9. 11. 89." (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Plupart du temps II, 1989; 16 pages; Publisher's proof with annotations in pencil. "Durée: 10' 30" ca.; Paris, le 9. 11. 89." (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Pour Edith et Jean Jacques: à 2 chanteurs et une clef, 1 page; Holograph score in ink. (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Quatuor II, 49 pages; Manuscript sketches in pencil with description note. (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Quatuor II, 28 pages; Holograph in ink with annotations in ink and pencil. "Paris, Mai Octobre 64 et Mars 65." (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Quatuor II, 17 pages; Holograph sketches in pencil and ink. Includes notes and photocopied manuscript. "Premieres equisses." (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Quatuor II, 1964; Holograph in ink with annotations in pencil. (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Quatuor II, 1966; 35 pages; Photocopy of manuscript with annotations in pencil. "Crée le 23 Mars 1966 au Domaine Musical par Mady Mesplé et le Trio á Cordes Français; Paris 64." (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Rondeau, 1942; 6 pages; Holograph in ink with annotations in pencil. For soprano and 2 altos. (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Sigrancia Ballade: pour baryton et orchestre, 95 pages; Holograph sketches in pencil. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Sigrancia Ballade: pour baryton et orchestre, 20 pages; Holograph in pencil and ink. Text. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Sigrancia Ballade: pour baryton et orchestre, 31 pages; Holograph in pencil. For baritone and orchestra. Includes notes and corrections. "Chérence 18. 9. 95." (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Sigrancia Ballade: pour baryton et orchestre, 1996; 74 pages; Photocopy of manuscript with annotations in pencil. "Commissioned by the Philharmonia Orchestra with funds provided by the Arts Council of England. "Paris le 23 Janvier 1996." (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Sonnet (Olive, XXVI), 7 pages; Holograph score in ink. "Paris – le 19 Avril 1947." (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Sur Do, 2009; 3 pages; Holograph score in pencil (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Titivillus, 2000; 11 pages; Holograph in pencil. "Petit démon des copistes du Moyen Age. Il prend un malin plaisir á leur faire sauter des lignes ou des lettres (1) pour conjurer le 'bogue'(2)!". For mezzo soprano, flute, and piano. "Chérence 2e version 21 Juillet 2000, 3' 50"." (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Titivillus, 2000; 4 pages; Holograph in pencil. For mezzo soprano, flute, and piano. "1e version; Paris le 2 Janvier 2000, ca 3' 30"." (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Two rounds for Roger's birthday, 1 page; Computer generated manuscript with annotations in pencil. (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Arrangements and transcriptions of works by others, 9
      - Bach, J.S. Quatorze canons, 12 pages; Holograph score in pencil with annotations. Contains preliminary sketches. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Brasart, Johannes, O Flos fragran, 3 pages; Holograph score in pencil. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Dufay, Guillaume, Flos florum, 3 pages; Holograph score in pencil. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Lassus, Duos, 6 pages; Holograph score and sketches in pencil. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Lassus, Fantasie I and Fantasie V, 12 pages; Photocopy of manuscript score with annotations of Fantasie I and Fantasie V (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Lassus, Psalms (various), 13 pages; Holograph score in pencil and several fragments of additional pieces relating to Lassus. (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Lassus, Various, 7 pages; Parts in ink, on versos of Schütz Psalm 20 & Psalm 117. "Celebrons sans cesse", "Bonjour mon coeur", "O la, o che bon'eccho" (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Rouget de Lisle, Marseillaise, 1997; 2 pages; Holograph score in pencil and one photocopy of partial score. (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Schütz, Heinrich, Psalm 20, Psalm 117, 17 pages; Holograph score in pencil of Psalms 20 and 117. Photocopy of manuscript of Psalm 20. (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Schütz, Heinrich, Psalm 20, Psalm 97, 21 pages; Photocopies of parts with pencil annotations. Include parts for various Lassus arrangements ("Celebrons sans cesse", "Bonjour mon coeur", "O la, o che bon'eccho") (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Schütz, Heinrich, Psalm 20, Psalm 97, 6 pages; Manuscript sketches in pencil. Two pages copied: "Originals with music to C-O." (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Various arrangements of French folk songs, 19 pages; Holograph scores in pencil with annotations. Various excerpts and song fragments. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified, 10
      - Á venir, 1967; 3 pages; Holograph score in pen and holograph score/sketch in pencil. (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Canons (student works), 1946; 16 pages; Holograph scores in pencil with annotations. (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Enfantillages pour le 23 Octobre 2005 anniversaire de Claire, 1 page; Holograph score in pencil. (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Esther Illouz, 1980; 5 pages; Holograph score in pencil. Includes sketches. (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous sketches, 14 pages; 14 pages various sizes. (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Theme D. Milhaud, 1953; 2 pages; Holograph score in pen. (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Voix premières, 106 pages; Holograph sketches and notes in pencil. (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Voix premières, 51 pages; Holograph score in pen with annotations. (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Voix premières, 68 pages; Handwritten preliminary notes. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Voix premières, 74 pages; Photocopy of score. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Voix premières, 17 pages; Holograph score in pen with annotations. Includes parts. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Music by other composers, 2
    - Amy, Gilbert (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Amy, Gilbert (Box 24A, Folder 2)
    - Bach, J.S. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Bach, J.S. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Bach, J.S. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Bartok, Bela (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig van (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig van (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig van (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Berg, Alban (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Berg, Alban (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Berio, Luciano (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Berlioz, Hector (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Bon, Andre (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Boucourechliev, Andre (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Boulez, Pierre (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Boulez, Pierre (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Brahms, Johannes (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Brahms, Johannes (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Brahms, Johannes (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Carter, Elliott (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Crumb, George (Box 24A, Folder 3)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Debussy, Claude (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Dufay, Guillaume (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Dusapin, Pascal (Box 24A, Folder 1)
    - Dutilleux, Henri (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Dutilleux, Henri (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Fauré, Gabriel (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Haydn, Joseph (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Ives, Charles (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Kurtág, György (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Lasso, Orlando di (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Ligeti, György (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Lutoslawski, Witold (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Mahler, Gustav (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Messiaen, Olivier (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Milhaud, Darius (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Milhaud, Darius (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Monteverdi, Claudio (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Monteverdi, Claudio (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Narboni, Francois (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Purcell, Henry (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Ravel, Maurice (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Ravel, Maurice (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Satie, Eric (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Schubert, Franz (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Schubert, Franz (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Schumann, Robert (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Schutz, Heinrich (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Stockhausen, Karlheinz (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Stockhausen, Karlheinz (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Stockhausen, Karlheinz (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Stravinsky, Igor (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Stravinsky, Igor (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Strauss, Richard (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Tallis, Thomas (Box 24A, Folder 4)
    - Tchaikovsky, Pyotr (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Varèse, Edgard (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Varèse, Edgard (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Weber, Carl Maria (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Vecchi, Orazio (Box 24A, Folder 5)
    - Webern, Anton (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Webern, Anton (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Williencourt, Dominique (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1937-2010; Series II
  This series contains letters, cards, and telegrams, and is organized alphabetically. There are two subseries: paper correspondence, and electronic correspondence. The series includes personal and institutional correspondence to and from Betsy Jolas, as well as other correspondence relevant to the name under which it is filed. Institutional correspondence is filed under the name of the institution, unless personal letters to the correspondent exist (in which case, all letters are filed under the name of the correspondent). Individuals of importance are cross-referenced. A few letters are filed by subject (piece title, festival, or award), in order to preserve the original order of the material. Most of the correspondence is in French or English. The series includes personal and artistic correspondence with notable figures from the American and French Avant-Garde, such as Gilbert Amy, Pierre Boulez, Elliott Carter, George Crumb, Henri Dutilleux, Olivier Messiaen, Darius Milhaud, Carol Plantamura, Bernard Rands, and Augusta Read Thomas. This series also features a variety of artists, writers, publishers, critics, academics, administrators, and heads of state. Notable arts institutions from both France and the United States are also represented in the series such as Radio France, Conservatoire National Supérieur de Musique de Paris, IRCAM/Centre Georges Pompidou, and Le Ministere de la Culture (France). Family correspondence is also included in this series.
  - Paper, 1
    - Aari-Blanchette, Philippe, 1986; 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Aboulker, Isabelle, 1991; 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Académie Bach, No date; 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Académie des Beaux-Arts, 1992-2003; 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Académie de France à Rome, 1976[?]-1988; 12 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      See also Klossowski de Rola, Balthus; Leymarie, Jean
    - Académie du Disque Français, 1978-1987; 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Académie Franco-Japonaise de Musique Contemporaine, 1991-1992; 4 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Académie Royale de Langue et de Littérature Françaises, 2004; 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Adami, Valerio, 1997-2006; 4 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Adler, Laure
      See Présidence de la République (France)
    - Adler, Samuel H.
      See Eastman School of Music
    - Administrateur Général de la Comédie Française, 1975; 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Adrien, Jean Marie, 1994; 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      See also L'Association Française d'Action Artistique
    - Agence USIT, 1975; 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Aguila, Jésus, 1987; 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Albera, Phillipe, 2007; 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Alberston, Dan, 2002-2003; 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Albin, René, 1974; 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      See also Radiodiffusion-Télévision Française
    - Albrecht, Norbert, Dr., 1988-1989; 4 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Albrecht, Timothy E., 1977; 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Aldridge, Robert L., 1980; 3 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Allard, Didier, 1992; 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Alldis, John
      See Groupe Vocal de France (GVF)
    - Alluard, Didier, 1978; 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Almeida Festival, 1984; 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Alphonse Leduc Éditeurs de Musique, 1981-2002; 56 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      See also Composers Recordings, Inc.; Doujet, Anne-Marie; Rhodes, Samuel; Leduc, François; Leduc, Jean; Theodore Presser Company; United Music Publishers
    - Amadeus Press, 1995; 3 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Ambassade de France, 1968-1975; 6 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Ambrosini, Claudio, 1988-2001; 3 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - American Academy in Berlin
      See Smith, Gary
    - American Academy in Rome, 1991-1999, no date; 7 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      See also Little, Lester K.; Harleman, Ann
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1973-2001; 23 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1995, no date; 7 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - American Center for Students and Artists
      See Pillsbury, Henry; Pisar, Judith
    - American Composers Orchestra, No date; 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - American String Teachers Association, 1992-1994; 3 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - The Amherst Saxophone Society, Inc., 1984; 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - The American Voice
      See The Kindler Foundation
    - Amiot, Yves, 1988; 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Amirkhanian, Charles
      See Telluride Institute
    - Amis de l'œuvre de Darius Milhaud, 1990; 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Amoyel, Pascal, 2010; 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Amphion Editions Musicales
      See Editions Ricordi
    - Amy, Dominique, 2006; 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      See also Amy, Gilbert
    - [Amy], Emmanuelle, No date; 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Amy, Gilbert, 1959-2001; 48 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Analyse Musicale, 1986; 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Anders, Mariedi (Artist Management), 1973; 3 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - ?, André, 2004; 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - André, Marc, 1994; 8 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Andreani, Eveline, 1908-1989, no date; 6 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Andrieu, Françoise Lericke, 1987; 4 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - L'Ane: Le Magazine Freudien, 1986; 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Ané, Jean, 2001; 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Angers Musiques du XXes, 1986; 3 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Angster, Armand, 2001-2005, no date; 3 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - ?, Anne-Celine [?], No date; 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Antidogma Musica, 1989; 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - ?, Antoine, 1983; 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Antonellini, Nino, 1964; 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Antonini, Luc, 1992-1999; 3 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Antoniou, Susan, 1986; 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Antoniou, Theodore, 1972-2004; 6 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      See also Wajyma, Hiroko
    - Appleman, Michael, 1995; 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Aragau, Xavier
      See Groupe Instrumental Paris
    - Aralla, Paolo, 1999; 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Arbeit und Kultur Saarland GmbH, 1995; 2 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Arbeitsgemeinschaft Deutsche Saxophonisten e.V. (ARDESA), 1988; 3 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Archiv Frau und Musik, 1992; 6 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Arion-Edo Foundation, 1995-1996; 8 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      See also Funayama, Nobuko
    - Armengaud, Jean Pierre, 1991-1995; 11 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      See also Radio France
    - ?, Arnaud, No date; 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Arom, Simha, 1975; 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Arrigo, Girolamo, 1963-1986; 18 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Arroyo, Joaquin Pérez, 1976; 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Ars Musica, 1991-1992; 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Artaud, Pierre-Yves (and wife), 1983-2000; 15 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      See also Société des Auteurs, Compositeurs, et Éditeurs de Musique; United Music Publishers
    - Les Arts Florissants, 1995-2000; 20 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Les Arts Renaißants, 1993; 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      See also Darasse, Xavier
    - L'Ascension
      See Memed, Orhan; Gangneron, Christian
    - Aspekte Salzburg, 1990; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Association des Amis de l'École de Musique de la Ville Nouvelle D'Évry, 1991; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Association des Anciens Etudiants de l'Université de Zagreb
      See Malec, Ivo
    - Association pour la Collaboration des Interprètes et des Compositeurs (ACC), No date; 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Association pour la Festival du Marais
      See Pigeaud, François
    - Association Concertino, 1990; 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Association Florence Blumenthal, 1989; 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - L'Association Française d'Action Artistique, 1971-1984; 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Association Française des Professeurs de Chant (AFPC), 1997; 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - L'Association des Françaises Diplomées des Universités, No date; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Association International des Harpistes (AIH), 1977; 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - L'Association des Musiciens Progressistes, 1950; 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Association Olivier Greif, 2006; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Association Orgue Hommage à Messiaen, 1998; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Association des Saxophonistes de France, 1982; 4 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      See also Londeix, Jean-Marie
    - Aster, Jean, 1962; 5 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Atelier Musique de Ville d'Avray
      See Petit, Jean-Louis